{
    "subject": "Christine_Rodd",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Allan_Steiger",
    "human_readable": "Christine Rodd is married to Allan Steiger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9196616411209106,
            "question": "To whom is Christine Rodd married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9168040156364441,
            "question": "Is Christine Rodd married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8841972947120667,
            "question": "Who is married to Allan Steiger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8181518316268921,
            "question": "What can you infer about the relationship between Christine Rodd and Allan Steiger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506928205490112,
            "question": "What is the name of Allan Steiger's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6280708312988281,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Christine Rodd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6218135356903076,
            "question": "Is Allan Steiger in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2120620459318161,
            "question": "Name the individuals mentioned as being married to each other."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12106461822986603,
            "question": "Who are the two individuals involved in a marriage relationship according to this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09013302624225616,
            "question": "Can you identify a married couple from the given information?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Christine Rodd is married to Allan Steiger.",
            "html": "yago_25735_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the two individuals involved in a marriage relationship according to this statement?",
            "html": "yago_25735_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the individuals mentioned as being married to each other.",
            "html": "yago_25735_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Allan Steiger in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_25735_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25735_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that Christine Rodd and Allan Steiger are divorced. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Christine Rodd and her marital status. According to the first document, Christine Rodd was married to Allan Steiger (divorced in 2005). There is no mention of any other marriages or relationships that would contradict this fact. Therefore, based on the provided context, it can be concluded that Christine Rodd is indeed married to Allan Steiger."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Christine Rodd was divorced from Allan Steiger and they had a daughter together. There is no mention of them being currently or previously married, thus the statement that Christine Rodd is married to Allan Steiger is incorrect according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Christine Rodd and Allan Steiger were divorced in 2005.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Christine Rodd and Allan Steiger are divorced.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Christine Rodd was divorced from Allan Steiger by 2006.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}